Council on Foreign Relations Digital Sound Recordings, 1953-1989: Finding Aid MC104.13
Public Policy Papers
- Series 1: Digital Sound Recordings, 1953-1989; 24 boxes
  - Global Interdependence and Science, 1983 November 1; Thomas, Lewis, 1913-1993; 1 box (Box 743)
    He began his investigative work as a Tilney Memorial Fellow at Thorndike Lab, Boston City Hospital (1941-1942), and in 1942 joined the Naval Medical Research Unit at Rockefeller Institute, studying infectious diseases of importance to the armed forces for the next four years. Also at this time, on January 1, 1941, he married Beryl Dawson. During these years Dr. Thomas began publishing some important scientific papers, the earliest material in this collection.
    In 1946, Dr. Thomas moved to Johns Hopkins University as an assistant professor of pediatrics, where he initiated a series of investigations on acute rheumatic fever. He continued this work as an associate professor at Tulane University for the next two years (1948-1950). In 1948 he published a paper on the Schwartzmann Phenomenon, a subject of significant scientific importance. He became a full professor of medicine at Tulane in 1950, and the same year moved again for four years (1950-1954) to the University of Minnesota to be a professor of pediatrics and medicine and director of pediatric research laboratories at Heart Hospital.
    Dr. Thomas went to New York University in 1954 where he was professor of pathology until 1969. Pathology became his main interest, and he was publishing papers of this nature during those years on such subjects as cortisone and infection, serum sickness, and drug allergy, as well as many papers on endotoxin.
    In 1973, Lewis Thomas became president of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center in New York City and chancellor in 1980. During these years he guided the Center and served on many of its committees, such as the Subcommittee on Informed Consent, the Standing Committee of the Medical Board, the Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, and the Sloan-Kettering Institute Senate and its Board of Scientific Consultants. He also received copies of reports, minutes, and correspondence related to other committees in which he was not directly involved, thereby allowing him to oversee all aspects of the Center. The years of his presidency and chancellorship saw many grants bestowed on the Center by the American Cancer Society and the Rockefeller family, to name a few; many grants given by MSKCC to other research centers such as the Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; and major corporate reorganizations and additions, such as the creation of a joint library facility for Rockefeller University, Cornell University Medical College, and MSKCC, a joint genetics department with Cornell University Medical College at Sloan-Kettering Institute, and the dedication of a new hospital in November 1973. Dr. Thomas served on various other joint committees to further these ends.
    When he left MSKCC in 1983 for the State University of New York at Stony Brook to be a professor, he was no less active. He was on various boards of corporations and non-profit organizations, some spanning the years at MSKCC and beyond: Biocyte Corporation (board member, 1984-1990), the Aaron Diamond Foundation (1985-1990), Monell Chemical Senses Center (1979-1991), and the National Research Council (1986-1988), among others. Dr. Thomas also served as "communicator" to the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, which involved submitting scientific papers by others to a review committee for possible publication in the Proceedings.
    Lewis Thomas is probably best known to the public from his column in The New England Journal of Medicine, "Notes of a Biology Watcher," which appeared from 1971 to 1980, and from the resulting book-length compilations of these essays, The Lives of a Cell (1974) and The Medusa and the Snail (1979). Dr. Thomas has published a number of other books, such as The Youngest Science: Notes of a Medicine Watcher (1983), Late Night Thoughts on Listening to Mahler's Ninth Symphony (1983), Et Cetera, Et Cetera: Notes of a Word Watcher (1990), and The Fragile Species (1992), as well as a plethora of articles and essays. These works, expressed in an informal friendly tone, earned him the National Book Award for The Lives of a Cell, the American Book Award for The Medusa and the Snail (1981), and many other literary awards, as well as recognition for being one of the best modern scientific essayists who writes non-technically about the meaning of biology and, by extension, the meaning of life.
    As the collection reflects (from 1966 to 1990), Dr. Thomas was much in demand as a speaker and lecturer in this country and abroad. He presented papers and gave speeches and commencement addresses, many of which found their way into widely-known medical journals and popular magazines. Among the many honors Dr. Thomas has received are the American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters Award (May 1980) and the coveted Woodrow Wilson Award (February 1981). In April of 1986 Princeton University honored him by naming its new molecular biology building the "Lewis Thomas Laboratory." In addition, Dr. Thomas has received 20 honorary degrees in science, law, letters, and music. A few of them are from Yale University, the University of Rochester, Princeton University, Johns Hopkins University, the Medical College of Ohio, and Reed College.
    Nov. 25, 1913 Born in Flushing, New York
    1933 B.S., Princeton University
    1937 M.D., Harvard University
    1937-1939 Intern, Boston City Hospital
    1939-1941 Resident in neurology, Neurological Institute, NYC
    1941-1942 Tilney Memorial Fellow at Thorndike Lab, Boston City Hospital
    1942-1946 Visiting investigator, Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
    1946-1948 Assistant professor of pediatrics, Johns Hopkins University
    1948-1950 Associate professor, Tulane University, New Orleans
    1948-1950 Director of Division of Infectious Disease, Tulane
    1950 Professor of medicine, Tulane
    1950-1954 Professor of pediatrics and medicine and director of pediatric research laboratories at Heart Hospital, University of Minnesota
    1954-1969 Professor of pathology, New York University
    1954-1958 Head of department, New York University
    1959-1966 Director of University Hospital
    1966-1969 Dean of School of Medicine, New York University
    1969-1973 Professor of pathology and head of department, Yale University
    1971-1973 Dean, Yale University School of Medicine
    1973-1980 President, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, NYC
    1974 Published The Lives of a Cell
    1979 Published The Medusa and the Snail
    1980-1983 Chancellor, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, NYC
    1983 President Emeritus, MSKCC
    1983 University professor, State University of New York, Stony Brook
    1983 Published The Youngest Science: Notes of a Medicine Watcher
    1983 Published Late Night Thoughts on Listening to Mahler's Ninth Symphony
    1988 Adjunct professor of medicine, NYU School of Medicine
    1988 Scholar-in-Residence, Cornell University Medical College
    1988 President, New York Academy of Science (council, 1966-1972)
    1990 Published Et Cetera, Et Cetera: Notes of a Word Watcher
    1992 Published The Fragile Species
  - Global Interdependence and Science, 1983 November 1; Thomas, Lewis, 1913-1993; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-206.2
  - Dinner in Honor of Zhao Ziyang: China, Foreign Policy, and United States-China Relations, 1984 January 15; Kissinger, Henry, 1923-; Zhao, Ziyang; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-207
    Portions of the speech are in Chinese.
  - Practical Barriers to a Consistent Foreign Policy, 1983 November 2; Mathias, Charles Mc., Jr; McPherson, Harry.; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-208
    Drop out at 28:03 for 48 seconds.
  - Human Health and Foreign Policy, Scientific Frontiers and National Frontiers: A Look Ahead, Elihu Root Lecture Series, 2nd Meeting, 1983 November 3; Thomas, Lewis, 1913-1993; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-209A
  - Untitled, undated; Haig, Alexander; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-209B
  - Council Town Meeting On Lebanon, 1983 November 7; Lord, Winston; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-210
  - Anglo-American Relations, 1983 November 30; Owen, David; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-211
  - Principles of Israeli Foreign and Security Policy, 1983 November 30; Janklow, Morton; Peres, Shimʿon 1923-2016; 1 box (Box 743)
    MC104-212
  - Current Situation in the Caribbean and Prospects for the Future, 1983 December 19; Adams, J. M. G.; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-213
  - Negotiating with the Russians, 1983 December 22; Lord, Winston; Nitze, Paul; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-214
    Drop out at 24:18 for 20 seconds.
  - Dinner in Honor Of Grace Darling, 1984 January 24; Griffith, Grace Darling; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-215
    Drop out at 40:49.
  - Peace in the Middle East, 1984 January 30; Bin Sultan, Bandar, Prince; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-216
  - Arms Control - Breaking the Deadlock, 1986 March 3; Smith, Gerard C.; Warnke, Paul C. (Paul Culliton), 1920-2001; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-217
  - Democracy in Argentina and Its Significance for Latin America, 1984 April 10; Caputo, Dante Mario; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-218
    Portions of this session are not in English.
  - Central America: Coming to Terms with the Endless War, 1984 May 14; Dickey, Christopher.; Johnstone, L. Craig; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-219
    Drop-out at 29 minute, for 43 seconds.
  - The Last Dozen Years: What Might We Learn?, 1984 May 24; Bundy, William P., 1917-2000; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-220
    William Putnam Bundy was born September 24, 1917 in Washington, D.C. to Harvey H. and Katherine (Putnam) Bundy. He was educated at Groton School (1935), Yale College (1939), Harvard Graduate School (1940) and Harvard Law School (1947). In 1943, he married Mary Acheson, daughter of Dean Acheson, secretary of state under President Harry Truman. Later, they had three children, two sons, Michael, and Christopher, and a daughter, Carol. He served in the United State's Army from 1941 to 1946. During World War II, he commanded an Army Signal Corps unit working with the British at Bletchley Park on the ULTRA operation breaking high-level German Engima ciphers. He was awarded the Legion of Merit and was made a member of the Order of the British Empire. After finishing law school in 1947, he worked for four years with the Washington, D.C. firm of Covington and Burling. In 1951, he joined the Central Intelligence Agency, Office of National Estimates, working as the chief of staff and as a liaison to the National Security Council staff. In 1960, Bundy served as staff director of the President's Commission on National Goals.
    Bundy served under President Kennedy and Johnson as a political appointee from 1961-1969. In 1961, he was appointed as Deputy Assistant Secretary of Defense for International Security Affairs (ISA), then from 1963 to 1964 as Assistant Secretary of Defense, ISA. From 1964-1969, he served under the Department of State as the Assistant Secretary for East Asian and Pacific Affairs. During his time as Assistant Secretary, Bundy participated in deliberations on such matters as the Bay of Pigs invasion and the Cuban Missile Crisis. Later, he became a central figure in shaping Vietnam policy. Bundy left government in May 1969 to teach at the Center for International Studies at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. From 1970 to 1972, he served as a part-time columnist for Newsweek, rotating with George Ball and Zbigniew Brzezinski in the international edition and briefly in the domestic edition.
    He edited Foreign Affairs from 1972 to 1984, contributing several articles of his own. Later he served as a Visiting Professor at the Woodrow Wilson School at Princeton University from 1985 to 1987. He was a Trustee of the American Assembly from 1964 to 1984 and served on the Board of Directors of the Council on Foreign Relations from 1964 to 1972. After 1987, he devoted his time to writing a critical history of American foreign policy in the Nixon-Kissinger Era including the later years of Vietnam. In 1998, he published A Tangled Web: the Making of Foreign Policy in the Nixon Presidency. Bundy died from heart trouble on October 6, 2000 at age 83.
  - Dinner in Honor of William P. Bundy, 1984 June 5; Bundy, William P., 1917-2000; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-221
  - International Monetary System, undated; Rosen, Robert; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-222
  - The Lessons of Lebanon, 1984 September 17; Friedman, Thomas L.; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-223
  - Central America: What Do We Do About the Process of Bringing Stability to that Part of the World, undated; Babbitt, Bruce; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-224
  - Untitled, undated; Dickey, Christopher.; McQuade, Margaret Osmer; 1 box (Box 744)
    MC104-225
    After 39:30, the audio is from a separate meeting.
  - A Conversation with the Secretary of State, 1984 October 1; Shultz, George P.; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-226
  - United States' International Trade Policy, 1986 February 19; Smart, S. Bruce; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-227
  - Narcotics: New Challenges to Latin America, 1986 February 10; Abrams, Elliott, 1948-; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-228
  - Trade Problems of the Movie Industry, 1985 December 4; Valenti, Jack.; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-229
    After 21:50, the audio is from a separate meeting.
  - Conversation with the President of the Federal Reserve Bank, 1985 December 3; Corrigan, E. Gerald.; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-230
  - Japan's New Challenge: Corporate Strategies, 1985 November 14; Kobayashi, Yotaro; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-231
  - The Strategies of the Terrorist Conflict, 1985 January 28; Sterling, Claire.; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-232
  - Special Luncheon Meeting: Henry Kissinger Talk, 1985 January 30; Kissinger, Henry, 1923-; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-233
  - A Conversation with the Prime Minister, 1985 March 28; Özal, Turgut; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-234
    Very poor recording.
  - McCloy Dinner, 1985 April 3; Kissinger, Henry, 1923-; McCloy, John J. (John Jay), 1895-1989; Rockefeller, David, 1915-2017; Schmidt, Helmut; Stone, Shepard; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-235
  - Future European-American Relations, 1985 April 4; Schmidt, Helmut; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-236
  - Remarks on East-West Relations, 1985 April 24; Brandt, Willy, 1913-1992.; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-237
    Drop-out at 24:20 for 3:02; another drop-out at 39:31 for 3:47.
  - Key Issues in American Foreign Policy, 1985 May 7; Brzeziński, Zbigniew (1928-2017).; Lord, Winston; 1 box (Box 745)
    MC104-238
  - Reducing the Risk of Nuclear War: Is Star Wars a Step in the Right Direction?, New Members' Meeting and Dinner, 1985 May 30; McNamara, Robert S., 1916-2009.; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-239
  - What Should Europe and the U.S. Do About the World's Monetary Problems?, 1985 June 18; D'Estaing, Valery Giscard; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-240
  - Farewell Reception in Honor of Winston and Bette Lord, 1985 June 26; Lord, Bette; Lord, Winston; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-241
  - Israel's Quest for Stability and Peace, 1985 October 3; Shamir, Itzhak, 1915-2012; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-242A
  - Untitled, undated; Ojeda, Mario; Purcell, Susan K.; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-242B
  - Lebanon: From Turmoil to Peace, 1985 October 21; Jumayyil, Amīn; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-243A
  - A Conversation with President Dos Santos, 1985 October 23; Santos, José Eduardo dos, 1942-; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-244A
  - Issues in United States Relations with Europe and Canada, New Members' Dinner, 1985 December 5; Ridgway, Rozanne Lejeune; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-245
  - International Trade Policy, 1986 January 8; Yeutter, Clayton K., 1930-2017; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-246
  - My Mission in Germany, Elihu Root Lecture, 1986 February 6; Burns, Arthur F. (Arthur Frank), 1904-1987; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-247
  - The Future of American-German Relations, Elihu Root Lectures, 1986 February 13; Burns, Arthur F. (Arthur Frank), 1904-1987; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-248.1
  - The Future of American-German Relations, Elihu Root Lectures, 1986 February 13; Burns, Arthur F. (Arthur Frank), 1904-1987; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-248.2
  - Iran-Iraq War, undated; ʿAzīz, Ṭāriq; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-249
    The beginning of the program records the introduction of the new president of the Council on Foreign Relations, Peter Tarnoff. The majority of the program is Tariq Aziz.
  - The Strategic Defense Initiative, 1986 March 6; Abrahamson, James A.; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-250.1
  - The Strategic Defense Initiative, 1986 March 6; Abrahamson, James A.; 1 box (Box 746)
    MC104-250.2
  - Dinner in Honor of Peter Tarnoff, 1986 April 30; Tarnoff, Peter; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-251
  - Dinner in Honor of Peter Tarnoff, 1986 April 30; Tarnoff, Peter; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-252
  - The Current French Political Scene, 1986 May 1; Fabius, Laurent; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-253
  - Peace in the Middle East, 1986 May 5; El-Baz, Osama; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-254
  - New Prospects for the European Economic Community, 1986 May 22; Barre, Raymond; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-255
  - Middle East Peace Prospects, 1985 May 22; Murphy, Richard W. (Richard William), 1929-; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-256
  - Arms Control and Implications of Soviet Non-Compliance, 1986 June 2; Holmes, H. Allen, 1933-; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-257
  - U.S.-China Relations, 1986 June 3; Lord, Winston; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-258
    Several false starts before program begins. Recording interrupted at 28:38 before question and answer session, resumed at closing remarks.
  - American-Soviet Relations, 1986 September 24; Hartman, Arthur A. (Arthur Adair), 1926-; Rice, Condoleezza; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-259
  - East-West Relations, 1986 September 25; Raimond, Jean-Bernard; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-260
    Drop out at 21:43 for 1:18.
  - United States Policy Towards Africa, 1986 September 30; Jackson, Jesse; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-261
  - Fiscal and Financial Outlook, 1986 October 28; Stockman, David; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-262
  - European Stagnation: Some Possible Remedies, 1986 November 17; Modigliani, Franco; 1 box (Box 747)
    MC104-263
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Eagleburger, Lawrence S.; Kagan, Robert; King, Edward; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-264A.1
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Eagleburger, Lawrence S.; Kagan, Robert; King, Edward; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-264A.2
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Eagleburger, Lawrence S.; Solomon, Richard H.; Whiting, Allen S. (Allen Suess), 1926-; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-264B.1
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Eagleburger, Lawrence S.; Solomon, Richard H.; Whiting, Allen S. (Allen Suess), 1926-; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-264B.2
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Kirkpatrick, Jeane J.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-265A.1
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Kirkpatrick, Jeane J.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-265A.2
  - The Reagan Doctrine: Intervention and Containment, 1986 November 21; Dalley, George A.; Eagleburger, Lawrence S.; Murdock, Clark A.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-265B
  - Soviet-American Relations, Members and Spouses Meeting, 1986 December 10; Dubinin, I︠U︡riĭ Vladimirovich; Schneier, Arthur; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-266
  - United States-Soviet Relations, 1986 December 12; Daniloff, Nicholas, 1934-; Gilmore, Kenneth; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-267
  - A Conversation with Archbishop Tutu, 1986 December 16; Tutu, Desmond; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-268
  - United States' Policy in the Persian Gulf, 1987 November 2; Carlucci, Frank Charles, 1930-2018; Furcell, Danny; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-269.1
  - United States' Policy in the Persian Gulf, 1987 November 2; Carlucci, Frank Charles, 1930-2018; Furcell, Danny; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-269.2
  - Debate on I.N.F., 1987 November 5; Buckley, William F., Jr., 1925-2008; Gelb, Leslie H.; Hogue, James; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-270
  - A Pluralist World Economy and Technological Change, Elihu Root Lecture Series, 1st Lecture, 1987 November 30; Blumenthal, W. Michael, 1926-; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-271
    W. Michael Blumenthal is a businessperson and economic adviser who served as Secretary of the Treasury in the Carter Administration. He was born in Germany in 1926, and with his family escaped Germany for Shanghai in 1939. He emigrated to the United States in 1947 and received his B.Sc. from UC Berkeley in 1951. He received an M.P.A. in public affairs (1953) and an M.A. and Ph.D. in economics (1956) from Princeton University and went into business. Starting in 1961, Blumenthal served as deputy assistant secretary for economic affairs, and later as the president's deputy special representative for trade negotiations in both the Kennedy and Johnson administrations. He returned to the business world in 1967 to become president of Bendix Corporation. In 1977 Blumenthal was named Secretary of the Treasury under Jimmy Carter. He resigned from the position in 1979, returning to the private sector. He was chairman and CEO of Unisys at his retirement in 1990. Blumenthal is the author of The Invisible Wall: Germans and Jews: A Personal Exploration (1998) and From Exile to Washington: A Memoir of Leadership in the Twentieth Century (2013). Blumenthal was the Founding Director of the Jewish Museum Berlin in 1997, and served there until 2014. Source: New Start New Jersey Advisory Board biographical statement.
  - A Pluralist World Economy and Technological Change, Elihu Root Lecture Series, 2nd Lecture, 1987 December 1; Blumenthal, W. Michael, 1926-; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-272
  - A Pluralist World Economy and Technological Change, Elihu Root Lecture Series, 1987 December 3; Blumenthal, W. Michael, 1926-; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-273
  - A Conversation With Barber Conable, 1988 February 11; Conable, Barber B.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-275.1
  - A Conversation With Barber Conable, 1988 February 11; Conable, Barber B.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-275.2
  - Economic and Financial Challenges Ahead, 1988 March 10; Corrigan, E. Gerald.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-276.1
  - Economic and Financial Challenges Ahead, 1988 March 10; Corrigan, E. Gerald.; 1 box (Box 748)
    MC104-276.2
    Latin music after 12:21.
  - A Conversation with Yitzhak Shamir, 1988 March 21; Shamir, Itzhak, 1915-2012; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-277
  - Life as an Artist in the Soviet Union, 1988 March 22; Feltsman, Vladimir; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-278
  - A Conversation with Chun Doo Hwan, 1988 April 7; Hwan, Chun Doo; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-279
    spoken in Korean with consecutive translation; program cut off at end.
  - A Conversation with the Chairman, 1988 April 27; Greenspan, Alan; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-280
  - The Problems of Strategic Weapons in Soviet-American Relations, 1988 March 24; Karpov, Viktor P.; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-281.1
  - The Problems of Strategic Weapons in Soviet-American Relations, 1988 March 24; Karpov, Viktor P.; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-281.2
  - Reform in China: What Chinese Are Saying in Private About the Official Reforms, 1988 April 15; Lord, Bette; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-282
  - The State of the Alliance: a View from Europe, New Members' Meeting, 1988 May 11; Lord Carrington; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-283
  - The Peace Prospects in the Middle East, 1988 May 26; Brown, Dean; Prince Hassan; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-284
  - American Foreign Policy – Opportunities and Challenges, 1988 September 8; Powell, Colin L.; 1 box (Box 749)
    MC104-285